xnumtw@gmail.com xnum@GitHub

Jia-Jun is a professional software engineer specializing in C++ and Go. He first worked for Taipei Exchange, where he had experience in classical financial system. After that, he joined a blockchain startup as a senior developer and became team leader in charge of cryptocurrency exchange. Now in order to build competitive product, he is bringing cutting-edge technology to FinTech startup.

Work Experience

Jan 2021-Present

Taichung, Taiwan

Stranity Technology Co., Ltd. Chief Technology Officer

spin-off

- Designed a Golang monorepo for the backend team and introduced clean architecture.
- Developed an automatic Swagger API documentation generator tool for Gin Framework (Golang).
- Designed and developed a strategy subscription and trading platform targeting low latency and high concurrency. Based on a self-managed Kubernetes cluster.
- Deployed and Maintained self-managed high-availability Kubernetes cluster, OS, and network infrastructure.
- Developed trading system components using Modern C++ (boost, TBB)
- Researched and applied low-latency trading technology to products. (Solarflare and Mellanox kernel bypass library, kernel tuning, CPU microarchitecture, cache-friendly programming, lock-free and wait-free data structures)

July 2019-Jan 2021

Sky Mirror Technology Co., Ltd. VP of Engineering

Futures trading system development using C++17.

- Optimized the trading system to achieve microsecond trading speed by selecting the best data structure and redesigning the process execution flow.
- Redesigned core component from MVC to Layered Architecture to improve maintainability and testability.
- Implemented gRPC plugin that could call RPC in a single process to reduce network latency or avoid context switching.

June 2018-May 2019

COBINHOOD, Ltd. Lead Backend developer

Cryptocurrency exchange development.

- Streamlined Kubernetes deployment configuration to reduce monthly cost by over USD 10,000 on the Google Cloud Platform.
- Designed a new coin holder reward point system to reduce 99% of computing resources.
- Developed staking reward distribution service for hundreds of users.
- Implemented the Go version client library to integrate two blockchains (Monero, Tezos) in exchange.
- Improved testing with database/cache tuning to speed up 300%.

June 2017-June 2018

Taipei Exchange *Software Engineer*

Development of an emerging stock trading system.

- Proposed state-of-the-art stock trading system design based on RAFT consensus to remove commercial middleware dependency.
- Developed message dispatch proxy to adapt the trading system to web service.
- Optimized continuous data streaming system to be 110 times faster and solved critical race condition problems. And developed a drop-in replacement for it based on libuv.

Education

2015-2017

MSc, Institute of Computer Science and Engineering National Chiao Tung University BSc, Computer Science National Taichung University of Education

2011-2015